In my last video,
I shared eight steps
that you can use
to introduce a
guest speaker at
an online event.
In today's video, I'll
put those eight steps
to practice by
showing you how
to use it.
Let's dive in.
Hello. Hello. Welcome. Welcome to the Enterprise U Virtual Event.
I am super excited to have you here. Excited about all the amazing conversations
that we're gonna have today. Now, before we begin, let me remind you of one thing.
We won't be recording today's session.
This is a safe space
Here, there is no judgment,
no repercussions,
only
unconditional love,
Joining us today is a super woman and an amazing
visionary.
And when I say
amazing,
I mean it.
What's special about her is that she loves helping young adults just like you
to build your public speaking confidence.
She believes that the distance between you and everything you want is only
one communication away. As you listen to her story,
you'll notice
the power in your own voice.
Today, she'll be sharing her top storytelling and pitching tips to help you with your next business presentation
or job interview.
Let's welcome Molly Harrington.
Molly, it's so good to have you here. Thank you so much
for joining us. Now that you've seen my 8 steps into
action, go back to my previous video and hear those eight
steps again on how to introduce a guest speaker at a
virtual event. And when you're ready, you can go ahead and
implement them. If you like this video, be sure to subscribe,
share with a friend, and hit that like so I can continue making
more videos like this just for you. Have an amazing day,
and I'll see you on the next one.