what most people
don't know and
i've tried to
make this clear
before and i've
said it i've
effectively been offered
to sell my
sanity many times
you don't become
as influential as
i am with
the kind of
impressions i get
without large corporations
becoming very interested
in you i've
had very large
companies which i'm
not gonna name
come along and
say we want
you to sponsor
we wanna sponsor
you we want
you to sell
our product you
have to tone
down your opinions
don't talk about
this don't say
if you're asked
about this say
it this way
and we'll give
you $25,000,000
and you'll shake
the product around
and i said
no i don't
want your money
and they were
kinda like okay
well your decision
now if i
was sponsored by
a very very
large company
those very very
large companies wouldn't
allow the media
to do to
me what they're
doing because they'd
call the media
and say that's
our sponsor don't
do that that's
our guy it's
all a big
club all i
had to do
was sell my
sanity james all
i had to
do cut my
balls off take
the sanity out
my mind and
take the money